[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "category": "soccer",
        "question": "miroslav klose is the top scorer in world cup history but ... with how many goals?",
        "options": [
            "sixteen",
            "fifteen",
            "fourteen",
            "seventeen"
        ],
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "category": "soccer",
        "question": "which south american team has the most copa libertadores in its record?",
        "options": [
            "peñarol",
            "boca juniors",
            "estudiantes",
            "independiente"
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "category": "soccer",
        "question": "how many world cups are there between brazil, italy and germany?",
        "options": [
            "twelve",
            "eleven",
            "fourteen",
            "thirteen"
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "category": "soccer",
        "question": "what is leicester city's nickname?",
        "options": [
            "the foxes",
            "the cats",
            "the blues",
            "the wolves"
        ],
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "category": "soccer",
        "question": "which team is the most times winner of the uefa champions league?",
        "options": [
            "barcelona",
            "chelsea",
            "real madrid",
            "bayern múnich"
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "category": "history",
        "question": "question history 1",
        "options": [
            "option 1",
            "option 2",
            "option 3",
            "option 4"
        ],
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "category": "history",
        "question": "question history 2",
        "options": [
            "option 1",
            "option 2",
            "option 3",
            "option 4"
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "category": "history",
        "question": "question history 3",
        "options": [
            "option 1",
            "option 2",
            "option 3",
            "option 4"
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "category": "history",
        "question": "question history 4",
        "options": [
            "option 1",
            "option 2",
            "option 3",
            "option 4"
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "category": "history",
        "question": "question history 5",
        "options": [
            "option 1",
            "option 2",
            "option 3",
            "option 4"
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "category": "pop",
        "question": "question pop 1",
        "options": [
            "option 1",
            "option 2",
            "option 3",
            "option 4"
        ],
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "category": "pop",
        "question": "question pop 2",
        "options": [
            "option 1",
            "option 2",
            "option 3",
            "option 4"
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "category": "pop",
        "question": "question pop 3",
        "options": [
            "option 1",
            "option 2",
            "option 3",
            "option 4"
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "category": "pop",
        "question": "question pop 4",
        "options": [
            "option 1",
            "option 2",
            "option 3",
            "option 4"
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "category": "pop",
        "question": "question pop 5",
        "options": [
            "option 1",
            "option 2",
            "option 3",
            "option 4"
        ],
        "answer": 3
    }
]